<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[PersonalBlog]]></title><description><![CDATA[PersonalBlog]]></description><link>https://rohan175.github.io</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 21:07:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[An attempt to understand life ft. corona]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s here, So when you hear the term corona now-a-days, one immediately pictures numbers of cases, deaths, conspirasy thories or data on how…]]></description><link>https://rohan175.github.io/An-attempt-to-understand-life-ft.-corona/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://rohan175.github.io/An-attempt-to-understand-life-ft.-corona/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;It’s here, So when you hear the term corona now-a-days, one immediately pictures numbers of cases, deaths, conspirasy thories or data on how we are doomed / economy is craching. Very proud to say I have a friend of mine on the blog today, Corona Virus sir also famously known as COVID-19 by the diseease he spreads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Warning&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/em&gt; As mr. Corona is here, everyone do not wash your hand till end of the blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So Mr. Corona what an unprecedented success rate you have. Starting from rock bottom, a localalite in China to becoming an International franhise in less than 3 months!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Thank you very much for such a faboulos introdcution, but I didnt need it tho. I strictly belive in work so hard that your work speaks for you.&amp;quot; &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definelty, Definelty. I would try to get as much knowledge realted to success in life from you via our conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the day I heard about you I have been trying to understand numbers realted to you. Either it be how exponetetionally you are growing, methods by which mortal humans are trying to understand your growth etc.etc. Even I made a puny attempt to estimate how fast you will grow. What are your expectations from you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;See, you have to understand it&amp;#39;s not in my control. I am dependent on how my target audience aka Humans reacts. Even if they choose to wash their hands and stay isolated am gonna win based on their PANIC!&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting. So like everyone else your bussiness is also dependent on stupidity of Humans. Great choice.
So as you have already turned the stock markets upside down, How much do you think you are going to affect the economic ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Again, like your attempt to understand my numbers, this is also something **no human can predict**. Yah, make as many educated gusses you can, most of them are gonna become clickbaits for news nothing else!&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So Mr. Corona Even if those numbers are accurate what one as an individual can do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s where you are wrong. Even in larger schemes individual efforts seems insignificant. A system, an organization doesn&amp;#39;t works without individuals. And I have found most Humans don&amp;#39;t understand power they posses as a species.&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do you mean? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;This may sound pretensious but it&amp;#39;s not. How I am able to achieve exponetianl growth?

It&amp;#39;s simple, as an indivdiual in a single body, I try my best to grow. And I trust my fellow viruses that they would be doing their best as well. 

All you can do as an individual is strive to be best in whatever you are doing. 

Larger sytems, governments, economy at local or world level doesn&amp;#39;t care for your opnion. But that doesn&amp;#39;t mean your work is worthless, even if it can affect one more person if carries on and who knows one day you can also become pandemic!&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whoa, so you are giving a way to fight economic crisis which are about to come. But if humans fight it out that means you are going to loose!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s where you are wrong. First of all humans are too lazy, secondly they don&amp;#39;t understand not only thier work but work ethics, empathy towards others in whatever they do has chained effects.

They have to evolve as species to defeat me.&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You telling me, I can be a super spreader and would be affecting 1000s! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Yah, it&amp;#39;s your call to spread ethics, postivity, growth or me&amp;quot; (Corona winks ;) )&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wasn’t expecting such deep thoughts from a non-living thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;What makes you think you are living being and not just another simulation!&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On that note, what you understand of life as? I mean your persepctive on meaning of life??&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;There is no meaning to it, because no knows answer to that. 

Although, as most succesful startup of 2020, I would like to say, &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are no kings here… Noone really knows what they are doing, but as a group as a species we have created miracles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;And one of those miracle could be understaing life!&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess that’s a good note to end this interview on.
I hope you had fun Mr. Corona. Of Course, I will be linking all social media handles of sir down below,
Make sure you, Like, Share &amp;#x26; Subscribe Corona (although only on social media) &amp;#x26; this blog as well!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>